{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The colour of the pills in the Matrix were Blue and Yellow.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur\u014d Araki, the same person who directed the anime Highschool of the Dead.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Gadgets","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The Western Electric Model 500 telephone uses tone dialing to dial phone numbers.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"hard","question":"The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Television","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}